Mark Winston fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Research records, 1970 - 2014; F-174-4; 3.72 m of textual records 19 MB of textual records (electronic) 87 photographs 3,095 photographs: col. slides 40 sound recordings 14 moving images 2 multiple media documents; General note locations of special media: * Textual records in electronic form are l
  - Books, 1980 - 2014; F-174-4-4; 2.01 m of textual records 209 photographs: col. slides 40 sound recordings
    Textual records; Sound recordings; Photographic materials
    - The Biology of the Honey Bee, 1980 - 2005; F-174-4-4-1; 28 cm of textual records 3 sound recordings
      - Graphics - drafts, vol. 1, [198-]; F-174-4-4-1-1 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Graphics, vol. 2, [198-]; F-174-4-4-1-2 (Archival box - standard 174-68)
      - Graphics, vol. 3, [198-]; F-174-4-4-1-3 (Archival box - standard 174-68)
      - Publishers correspondence, 1981 - 1984; F-174-4-4-1-4 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Introduction, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-5 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 2: Origin and Evolution of Bees, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-6 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 3: Form and Function - Honey Bee Anatomy, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-7 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 4: Development and Nutrition, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-8 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 5: Nest Architecture, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-9 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 6: Division of Labour, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-10 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 7: Other Worker Activities, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-11 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 8: Pheromones, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-12 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 9: Communication and Orientation, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-13 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 10: Food, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-14 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 11: Swarming, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-15 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 12: Drones, Queens and Mating, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-16 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Chapter 13: Ecology, 1984 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-17 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Harvard Press, vol. 1, 1984 - 2005; F-174-4-4-1-18 (Archival box - standard 174-30)
      - Harvard Press, vol. 2, 1984 - 2005; F-174-4-4-1-19 (Archival box - standard 174-31)
      - Book chapter organization, 1985 - 1986; F-174-4-4-1-20 (Archival box - standard 174-31)
      - Book figures, 1985 - 1993; F-174-4-4-1-21 (Archival box - standard 174-31)
      - The Biology of the Honey Bee (published book), 1987; F-174-4-4-1-22 (Archival box - standard 174-31)
      - Book reviews, 1987 - 1996; F-174-4-4-1-23 (Archival box - standard 174-31)
      - La biologie de l'abeille (French translation), 1993; F-174-4-4-1-24 (Archival box - standard 174-69)
      - A Biolgia da Albelha (Portuguese translation), 2003; F-174-4-4-1-25 (Archival box - standard 174-31)
    - Killer Bees: The Africanized Honey Bee in the Americas, 1990 - 1996; F-174-4-4-2; 14 cm of textual records
      - Killer Bee annotated draft, [199-]; F-174-4-4-2-1 (Archival box - standard 174-31)
      - Notes and correspondence, 1990; F-174-4-4-2-2 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
      - Figures, 1990 - 1993; F-174-4-4-2-3 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
      - Harvard University Press correspondence, 1990 - 1994; F-174-4-4-2-4 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
      - Reviews and letters, 1991 - 1996; F-174-4-4-2-5 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
      - Book graphic negatives, 1992; F-174-4-4-2-6 (Archival box - small 174-63)
      - Book graphics, 1992; F-174-4-4-2-7 (Archival box - standard 174-69)
      - Book photos, 1992; F-174-4-4-2-8 (Archival box - small 174-63)
      - Chapter covers, 1992; F-174-4-4-2-9 (Archival box - standard 174-69)
      - Killer Bees: The Africanized Honey Bee in the Americas (published book), 1992; F-174-4-4-2-10 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
    - Nature Wars, 1990 - 2002; F-174-4-4-3; 76 cm of textual records 156 photographs: col. slides
      - Gypsy Moth: handouts, [199-]; F-174-4-4-3-1 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
      - Gypsy Moth: reports, vol. 1, [199-]; F-174-4-4-3-2 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
      - Gypsy Moth: reports, vol. 2, [199-]; F-174-4-4-3-3 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
      - Codling articles, [199-]; F-174-4-4-3-4 (Archival box - standard 174-32)
      - Gypsy Moth: contacts, [199-]; F-174-4-4-3-5 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Definitions of Science, [199-]; F-174-4-4-3-6 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Gypsy Moth: medical, 1991 - 1992; F-174-4-4-3-7 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Gypsy Moth: media, 1992 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-8 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Gypsy Moth: correspondence and notes, 1994; F-174-4-4-3-9 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Gypsy Moth: control, 1994; F-174-4-4-3-10 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Nature thought, 1994 - 1995; F-174-4-4-3-11 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Outline and graphics, 1994 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-12 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Pests, 1994 - 1997; F-174-4-4-3-13 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Home: correspondence and notes, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-14 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Home pests: brochures, vol. 1, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-15 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Home pests: brochures, vol. 2, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-16 (Archival box - standard 174-33)
      - Agriculture file: codling, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-17 (Archival box - standard 174-34)
      - Urban: correspondence and notes, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-18 (Archival box - standard 174-34)
      - Urban: brochures and handouts, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-19 (Archival box - standard 174-34)
      - Urban: products, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-20 (Archival box - standard 174-34)
      - Urban: articles, vol. 1, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-21 (Archival box - standard 174-34)
      - Urban: articles, vol. 2, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-22 (Archival box - standard 174-34)
      - Articles: home pesticide use, vol. 1, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-23 (Archival box - standard 174-34)
      - Articles: home pesticide use, vol. 2, 1995; F-174-4-4-3-24 (Archival box - standard 174-35)
      - Ideas, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-25 (Archival box - standard 174-35)
      - Rachel Carson, vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-26 (Archival box - standard 174-35)
      - Rachel Carson, vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-27 (Archival box - standard 174-35)
      - Beneficials, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-28 (Archival box - standard 174-35)
      - Transgenic: media and reports, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-29 (Archival box - standard 174-35)
      - Codling: brochures and handouts, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-30 (Archival box - standard 174-35)
      - Pheromones, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-31 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Transgenic: science, vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-32 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Transgenic: science, vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-33 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Talks, 1995 - 1998; F-174-4-4-3-34 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Publishers, 1995 - 2002; F-174-4-4-3-35 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Acknowledgements, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-36 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Background publications, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-37 (Archival box - standard 174-37)
      - Book draft, vol. 1, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-38 (Archival box - standard 174-69)
      - Book draft, vol. 2, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-39 (Archival box - standard 174-69)
      - Codling and mating disruption articles, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-40 (Archival box - standard 174-37)
      - Forest pests, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-41 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Pest ethics, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-42 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Revisions, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-43 (Archival box - standard 174-36)
      - Transgenic: products, 1996; F-174-4-4-3-44 (Archival box - standard 174-37)
      - Transgenic: resistance, 1996 - 1997; F-174-4-4-3-45 (Archival box - standard 174-37)
      - Reviews, vol. 1, 1996 - 1999; F-174-4-4-3-46 (Archival box - standard 174-37)
      - Reviews, vol. 2, 1996 - 1999; F-174-4-4-3-47 (Archival box - standard 174-37)
      - Nature Wars (published book), 1997; F-174-4-4-3-48 (Archival box - standard 174-37)
      - Book prizes, 1997 - 1998; F-174-4-4-3-49 (Archival box - standard 174-37)
      - Research notebook, vol. 1, 1994 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-50 (Archival box - small 174-75)
      - Research notebook, vol. 2, 1994 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-51 (Archival box - small 174-76)
      - Research notebook, vol. 3, 1994 - 1996; F-174-4-4-3-52 (Archival box - small 174-76)
      - Nature Wars, 1996 - 2002; F-174-4-4-3-53; 95 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - standard 174-96)
      - Nature Wars - talk, 1998; F-174-4-4-3-54; 61 photographs: col. slides 1 textual record (Archival box - standard 174-96)
        Slides include speaking notes.
    - From Where I Sit: Essays on Bees, Beekeeping and Science, 1996 - 1999; F-174-4-4-4; 7 cm of textual records
      - Reviews, 1996 - 1999; F-174-4-4-4-1 (Archival box - standard 174-66)
      - Publisher's correspondence, 1996 - 1999; F-174-4-4-4-2 (Archival box - standard 174-66)
      - Final draft with annotations, 1997; F-174-4-4-4-3 (Archival box - standard 174-66)
      - From Where I Sit: Essays on Bees, Beekeeping and Science (published book), 1997; F-174-4-4-4-4 (Archival box - standard 174-66)
    - Travels in the Genetically Modified Zone, 1998 - 2005; F-174-4-4-5; 73 cm of textual records 53 photographs: col. slides
      - Organic: correspondence and notes, vol. 1, 1998 - 2000; F-174-4-4-5-1 (Archival box - standard 174-66)
      - Organic: correspondence and notes, vol. 2, 1998 - 2000; F-174-4-4-5-2 (Archival box - standard 174-66)
      - Bioengineering: UK, 1998 - 2000; F-174-4-4-5-3 (Archival box - standard 174-66)
      - Bt and the problem of resistance, vol. 1, 1999 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-4 (Archival box - standard 174-38)
      - Bt and the problem of resistance, vol. 2, 1999 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-5 (Archival box - standard 174-38)
      - Bt and the problem of resistance, vol. 3, 1999 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-6 (Archival box - standard 174-38)
      - GM canola oil, vol. 1, 1999 - 2002; F-174-4-4-5-7 (Archival box - standard 174-38)
      - GM canola oil, vol. 2, 1999 - 2002; F-174-4-4-5-8 (Archival box - standard 174-38)
      - General preface/outline, 2000; F-174-4-4-5-9 (Archival box - standard 174-38)
      - Regulators, 2000; F-174-4-4-5-10 (Archival box - standard 174-39)
      - Environmental impacts, vol. 1, 2000; F-174-4-4-5-11 (Archival box - standard 174-39)
      - Environmental impacts, vol. 2, 2000; F-174-4-4-5-12 (Archival box - standard 174-39)
      - Environmental impacts, vol. 3, 2000; F-174-4-4-5-13 (Archival box - standard 174-39)
      - Third world, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-14 (Archival box - standard 174-39)
      - Third world, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-15 (Archival box - standard 174-40)
      - Third world, vol. 3, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-16 (Archival box - standard 174-40)
      - Consumers, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-17 (Archival box - standard 174-40)
      - Consumers, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-18 (Archival box - standard 174-40)
      - Researchers and the Science, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-19 (Archival box - standard 174-40)
      - Biological ethics and law, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-20 (Archival box - standard 174-41)
      - Biological ethics and law, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-21 (Archival box - standard 174-41)
      - Seeds/history, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-22 (Archival box - standard 174-41)
      - Seeds/history, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-23 (Archival box - standard 174-41)
      - Harvard Press correspondence and contracts, 2000 - 2005; F-174-4-4-5-24 (Archival box - standard 174-41)
      - Where are we going?, 2001 - 2003; F-174-4-4-5-25 (Archival box - standard 174-41)
      - Book draft, vol. 1, 2001; F-174-4-4-5-26 (Archival box - standard 174-69)
      - Book draft, vol. 2, 2001; F-174-4-4-5-27 (Archival box - standard 174-69)
      - Reviews, 2001 - 2004; F-174-4-4-5-28 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
      - Travels in the Genetically Modified Zone (published book), 2002; F-174-4-4-5-29 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
      - Awards, 2002; F-174-4-4-5-30 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
      - Travels in the Genetically Modified Zone (Japanese translation), 2005; F-174-4-4-5-31 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
      - Research notebook, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-32 (Archival box - small 174-76)
      - Research notebook, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-33 (Archival box - small 174-76)
      - Research notebook, vol. 3, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-34 (Archival box - small 174-77)
      - Research notebook, vol. 4, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-35 (Archival box - small 174-77)
      - Research notebook, vol. 5, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-36 (Archival box - small 174-77)
      - Research notebook, vol. 6, 2000 - 2001; F-174-4-4-5-37 (Archival box - small 174-77)
      - Talk: Travels in the Genetically Modified Zone, [ca. 2002]; F-174-4-4-5-38; 53 photographs: col. slides 1 textual record (Archival box - standard 174-96)
    - Travels in the Genetically Modified Zone audio interviews, 1990 - 1995; F-174-4-4-6; 37 sound recordings; Physical description: includes 39 audio cassettes (microcassette format).
      - Aventis, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-1 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3783)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item29.
      - NFU: Barber/Thomas, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-2 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3784)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item30.
      - K. Bloem, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-3 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3785)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item31.
      - Chalfen, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-4 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3786)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item32.
      - George Cherian/Dave Kryder, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-5 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3787)
        George Cherien; Kryder, Dave; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item33.
      - Percy Z/Bruce Dalgarno, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-6 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3788)
        Dalgarno, Bruce; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item34.
      - Darranance/Perceps, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-7 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3789)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item35.
      - Don Duvich, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-8 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3790)
        Don Duvich; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item36.
      - David Garst - seeds, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-9 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3791, Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3792)
        Garst, David; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item37.
      - Fred Gould, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-10 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3793)
        Fred Gould; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item39.
      - Jenny Hillard, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-11 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3794)
        Jenny Hillard; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item40.
      - Margaret Llewellyn, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-12 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3795)
        Margaret Llewellyn; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item41.
      - Sue Mayer, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-13 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3796)
        Sue Mayer; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item42.
      - Myers, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-14 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3797)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item43.
      - Harold Ostenson, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-15 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3798)
        Harold Ostenson; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item44.
      - Robert Paarlberg, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-16 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3799)
        Robert Paarlberg; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item45.
      - Press Conference House of Commons, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-17 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3800)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item46.
      - Prob. Ecological Service, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-18 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3801)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item47.
      - Jane Rissler/Rebecca Goldberg/John Doll, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-19 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3802)
        Jane Rissler; Rebecca Goldberg; John Doll; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item48.
      - Jonothon Roskos, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-20 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3803)
        Jonothon Roskos; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item49.
      - Phil Unterschuetz, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-21 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3804)
        Phil Unterschuetz; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item50.
      - Roger Wechsler, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-22 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3805)
        Roger Wechsler; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item51.
      - Ray Wilfing, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-23 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3806)
        Ray Wilfing; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item52.
      - Crops, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-24 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3807)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item53.
      - Gilkeson, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-25 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3808)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item54.
      - Argyle, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-26 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3809)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item55.
      - Barb Edwards, [199-]; F-174-4-4-6-0-27 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3810)
        Edwards, Barb; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item56.
      - John Bell, Agriculture Canada, June 1994; F-174-4-4-6-0-28 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3811)
        John Bell; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item57.
      - David/Elizabeth Garst, 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-29 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3812, Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3813)
        Garst, David; Elizabeth Garst; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item58.
      - Conway/Bird and Keegan, April 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-30 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3814)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item60.
      - Vern Gilpin/Angelo Kouris, June 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-31 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3815)
        Kouris, Angelo; Vern Gilpin; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item61.
      - Steve Wong/Bob Wick, 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-32 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3816)
        Steve Wong; Wick, Bob; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item62.
      - George Kirton/Christine Webber, June 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-33 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3817)
        George Kirton; Webber, Christine; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item63.
      - Mike Mackintosh, July 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-34 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3818)
        Mike Mackintosh; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item64.
      - Liz Sundstrom/Glen Shrimpton, August 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-35 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3819)
        Liz Sundstrom; Glen Shrimpton; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item65.
      - Miller/Don Elliot, October 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-36 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3820)
        Don Elliot; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item66.
      - Linda Edwards, November 1995; F-174-4-4-6-0-37 (Audio cassette: microcassette OBJ-3821)
        Linda Edwards; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item67.
    - Bee Time: Lessons from the Hive, 2013 - 2014; F-174-4-4-7; 2.9 cm of textual records
      - Bee Time - uncorrected page proofs (bound), 2014; F-174-4-4-7-1 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
      - Bee Time - page proof mark ups April 2014, F-174-4-4-7-2 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
      - Dialogue in Bee Time: Lessons Learned from the Bees - Harvard Press reviews and draft, 2013; F-174-4-4-7-3 (Archival box - standard 174-85)
  - Conferences and presentations, 1981 - 2008; F-174-4-5; 31.4 cm of textual records 19 MB of textual records (electronic) 16 photographs (electronic) 477 photographs: col. slides
    Textual records; Photographic materials; Records in electronic form (born-digital)
    Most files and items in this sub-series are open with no restrictions. However, some may contain personal or confidential information. Files or items marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release. As a result of the review, access restrictions may apply.
    - Conferences/presentations, 1987; F-174-4-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - Conferences/presentations, 1990; F-174-4-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - Australia, 1991 - 1995; F-174-4-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - New Zealand, 1993 - 1995; F-174-4-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - Conferences/presentations, 1994; F-174-4-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - Westview Press, 1994 - 1997; F-174-4-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - Conferences/presentations, 1995; F-174-4-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - ANERCEA (France), 1995 - 1997; F-174-4-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - Conferences/presentations, 1996 - 1997; F-174-4-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-42)
    - Conferences/presentations, 1997 - 1998; F-174-4-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - Conferences/presentations, 1999; F-174-4-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - Select Standing Committee on Agriculture and Fisheries, 1999; F-174-4-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - Festival of the Written Arts, 1999 - 2000; F-174-4-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - Conferences/presentations, 2000; F-174-4-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - National Speakers Bureau: crop protection, 2000; F-174-4-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - National Speakers Bureau: crop protection slides, 2000; F-174-4-5-0-16 (Cd box 174-80, Optical disc: cd OBJ-1072)
      Consists of one digital file, a PowerPoint presentation.
    - Conferences/presentations, 2001; F-174-4-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - Crop Protection Institute Conference, 2001 - 2002; F-174-4-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - Conferences/presentations, vol. 1, 2001 - 2002; F-174-4-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - Conferences/presentations, vol. 2, 2001 - 2002; F-174-4-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - North Shore Counselling Centre, 2001 - 2002; F-174-4-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-43)
    - Conferences/presentations, 2003; F-174-4-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-73)